

CONTACT

- +30 6982109345
- ☑ yvosnakis@gmail.com
- Athens, Greece
- www.yvosnakis.com

EDUCATION

2021 - 2024 UNIVERSITY OF DERBY

• Computer Science BSc

2020 - 2021 UNIVERSITY OF EXETER

• Business BSc

2016 - 2018 INTERNATIONAL BACCALAUREATE

• 38 points

SKILLS

- Web Development
- Data Analytics
- Teamwork
- Programming Languages (C, C#, CPP, JS, HTML, CSS, Python)
- Time Management
- Effective Communication
- Critical Thinking

LANGUAGES

- English (Fluent)
- Greek (Fluent)
- Italian (Intermediate)
- Spanish (Basics)

YANNIS VOSNAKIS

COMPUTER SCIENCE GRADUATE

PROFILE

I'm a 24-year-old Computer Science BSc graduate with a passion for software development and a diverse background in customer service, education, and entrepreneurship. My journey through various roles has equipped me with a unique set of skills and a strong work ethic that I am eager to bring to a software development team.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Cambly Inc.

English Tutor

2022 - PRESENT

- Maintained organised files and documentation of each student's progress
- Provided optimal instruction and academic support to students
- Attended workshops and classes to further my professional skills
- Developed and implemented a well-rounded and age-appropriate curriculum

Centauro

2023 - 2023 (SEASONAL)

Fleet Manager and Rental Agent

 Utilised sales techniques and strategies to build customer relationships and close sales, resulting in being promoted to second in command

- Developed and implemented an efficient fleet management system that reduced vehicle downtime
- · Attention to detail as customer satisfaction was vital

PELAGOS SUPS

2022 - PRESENT

Founder

- Monitor and maintain brand consistency across all marketing channels and materials.
- Worked with strong attention to detail and excellent record-keeping abilities, breaking-even within the first 3 months
- Executed excellent management and entrepreneurial skills

REFERENCE

Vassilios Vogkas

University of Derby

Head of Computing Department

Email: v.vogkas@mc-class.gr